<Document>

  # The 50-Year War (2772)
  In the year 2772, almost 150 years after the start of the Corporate war, [textlink="The Imperial Coalition's" link="ImperialCoalition"] relationship with their citizens reached the lowest. Riots, protests, and strikes are happening all throughout the Coalition's territories, including the Triad Sector, grinding the sector's economy to a halt.
  This opens the path for opportunists such as the [textlink="Solarian Directive" link="SolarianDirective"]: [color=lightgreen]Jupiter[/color] to capitalize on the weakening grip of The Imperial Coalition. Soon after the arrival of the Solarian Directive, the Solarian Directive wastes no time in building up their presence in the sector.
  The Solarian Directives brings along a number of companies, with two main companies that directly affect the war efforts. There is Terralith Research & Manufacturing Center and Helios Power Solutions Inc.. Terralith Research & Manufacturing Center specializes in the development of cutting-edge weaponry, shielding, and heavy machinery. Beyond its R&D core, Terralith Research & Manufacturing Center oversees the production of the automated drone swarms used to maintain sector-wide blockades.
  Complementing this, Helios Power Solutions Inc. ensures operational longevity by managing fleet logistics, providing the essential fuel and energy reserves required for sustained combat. Meanwhile, the Imperial Mining Co. serves as the Coalition's lifeblood, providing the raw materials that keep their war machine grinding forward.
  The actions of the Solarian Directive upsets The Imperial Coalition's generals and governor, but they cannot take an initiative to drive them away due to the strained economy for the first few months, allowing the Solarian Directive able to get a stable enough footing and gain the favor of a lot of the Coalition's citizens hoping it could free them from the TIC's hold. A few months after the Solarian Directive's arrival, The Imperial Coalition recalled their non-combat fleet from nearby mining or expeditionary fleet to be retrofitted with weapons and repurposed as a military ship, able to make the first move to try and drive out the invaders, which sparked the start of a 40 year long war between the 2 sides.

  For those 50 long years, both factions faced a stalemate in establishing their influence into the sector. The Imperial Coalition is stunted due to the economy getting even more strained due to war efforts, forcing them to assume a more passive and defensive strategy.
  The Solarian Directive is also unable to grow beyond this point due to their supply lines being intercepted by the TIC and pirates that are bold enough, along with the extreme distance from the Sol System. Both sides rely on the support of the citizens, Most support the Solarian Directive due to them promising the citizens freedom and independence, but there are the rich 1% of citizens that benefited from the Coalition's mandates and policies that supported their local government, giving the two powers an equal chance of fighting each other.

</Document>
