<Document>

  # The False Hope (2814-2820)
  A few years after the formation of the CDF, a few more companies started to rise up to the spotlight. Some exploited the chaos for profit, some tried to help the conflict, and a few tried to run away from the hellscape.
  The companies are as follows:

  ## Prometheus Galactic Advisors Group (PGA Group)
  PGA Group, is the company which exploited the war for their own benefits and profits.
  They played with fire as played both sides, selling information to The Imperial Coalition about The Directive's technology and plans, also selling information to the Solarian Directives regarding the Coalition's battle plans and fleet locations.
  They used old Syndicate technology to assist them in their efforts.
  In 2817, the PGA Group collapsed after both the Solarian Directives and The Imperial Coalition discovered the organization's predatory double-agency. The discovery prompted independent, yet simultaneous, campaigns of extermination.
  Driven by a need for information security, the SD aimed to prevent further data hemorrhaging, while the empire acted to safeguard its empire's prestige and silence the dissenters. This cross-sector hunt persisted until every trace of the PGA Group was purged from existence.

  ## Lithos Research and Development Co. (LRD Co.)
  LRD Co. is a company that worked alongside the CDF to help with the war effort.
  They specialize in planetary mining, research and development, and planetary colonization even in the harshest climates.
  They supplied the CDF with materials for ship manufacturing, research for weapons tech, autonomous robots to be used for combat, as well as giving the CDF places to set up camp, recuperate, and refit no matter the circumstance.
  The company collapsed at the year 2820, due to constant mercenary raids, planetary bombardment by the opposing sides, and research gone wrong. The company could not keep up with upkeep and reparation costs, and thus faded away.

  ## Void Enigma Institute (VEI)
  VEI is a company that has little to no information regarding its research and findings.
  The only things that the company left behind are the year the institute was founded, what their original purpose was, the year of the disappearance, and some left over voice logs that got scattered all throughout the sector.
  VEI was founded at the height of the war, at the year 2819, the original goal was to find a way to stop the war or entirely move out of the sector, but at that time escape was impossible.
  Last traces of the institute date back to the year 2822, and since then there was no news regarding VEI.
  If one would come across any of VEI's findings either in paper or recordings, most will be heavily redacted, corrupted, or ruined. Whatever they found at the year 2822 was the cause of every data corruption, redaction, and expungement.

</Document>
